hi guys welcome to our youtube channel
to get notified please click subscribe
and hit that bell button for future
videos
so that you'll be updated once we upload
videos in our channel
all right for this video we're going to
walk you through and how to pay your
money life insurance using your video
online account
okay first step we need to open a web
browser in this case we're using a web
browser instead of the video online app
so type in video online
[Music]
all right and make sure that you are
accessing the right site for security
purposes
all right click on video online
we're recording here our screen using
our ipad
[Music]
just wait for a moment
okay
so you need to log in your user id and
your password
make sure you open https that's the
secured site
okay so let's start assuming that you're
able to log in using your video online
account
you'll be able to see there the home
page
[Music]
all right you can see there
under my accounts
send money pay bills reload
enrollment you need to click on
enrollment because we need to enroll the
builder first
and click on enroll
we need to enroll the company builder
first before we can pay your money life
all right company builder
[Music]
okay so
under company builder you can see their
different company builders
just look for money life insurance
corporation
okay so for subscriber number that's the
policy number
and subscriber name that's the name of
the owner or the insured
and you can input your preferred
nickname
make sure to click submit
all right and you need to go back once
you're able to click submit go back to
the home page
click on pay bills
and click bills payment
[Music]
okay click click on pay bills
all right you can see they're the
enrolled billers
all right look for
many life insurance corporation in this
case this is my own account in my life
my own insurance policy you can see
there your name and your subscriber
number in case you're able to enroll
your manulife policy
aside from manual life insurance
corporation
you can see here different builders
that i already enrolled in my video
online account
right you can also pay your video credit
card
and your electric bill
and this is how it looks like
once you're able to
paid your manulife policy successfully
thank you for watching this video and if
this video helps you
and gives you in more information please
don't forget click and subscribe
our channel so that you will be more
inspired to create more videos in the
future bye bye